Hey.
So, what do
you think?
New haircut?
Necklace?
Dress.
Boots?
Boots!
Yes! Now, they're a little
more than I usually spend
on boots, um...
or rent.
Oh, my God.
I know.
I'm going to miss being able
to afford food.
I'm sorry.
They just
looked so good.
And the saleswoman was
looking at me like
"These are way too
expensive for you."
She had a point.
( knocking on door )
Hi.
Hey.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Monica.
Those boots
are amazing!
They're mine!
Yeah, well, too bad we're going
to have to return them.
Return them?! Shh!
They're going
to hear you!
Honey, I'm not returning them,
okay?
I mean,
I know they cost a lot
but I'm going to wear them
all the time-- you'll see.
And besides,
I love the compliments.
I mean, have you ever had
something that was so beautiful
that everyone wants it?
I have you.
Nice try.
I'm keeping the boots.
Anyway, look...
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
That's right,
I love you...
and I'm going
to play with you
all the time.
How can you let him
talk to your crotch like that?
He's talking
to the baby.
Oh, okay!
Okay, 'cause when he said
"I can't wait to hear
your first words."
I thought, "There's a trick."
Okay... well, I got to go,
you guys.
I'll see you later.
Okay.
Okay. Bye.
Bye.
Oh, hey, Rach,
listen-- hi.
Hi.
Um, can you do
me a favor?
I was talking
to my sister
and she knows you
work at Ralph Lauren--
Forget it-- no way--
I am not sending
any more Ralph Lauren clothes
to prison; it is a waste.
No, no, no, no.
Not her, not her.
My youngest
sister, Deena--
she's really
interested in fashion
and she wants to talk
to someone successful
to, you know, give
her some advice.
I guess she could talk
to one of my supervisors.
No, no, no, she wants
to talk to you.
Really?
Oh, my God!
I'm successful.
So, will you
meet with her?
Yes, I'd love to.
Have her come by
the office.
Great. Thanks.
You're going to
love her so much.
And, oh, she's the
smartest of all the
Tribbiani children.
Yeah, you know
the SATs?
Yeah.
She took them.
Hey, Ross, doesn't Ben go
to Smithfield Day School?
Yeah, why?
Sting has a son
that goes there, too.
Yeah, I know.
He's in Ben's class.
You knew this
and you never said anything?
With all the stupid
dinosaur stuff you tell us?
Fine. No more dinosaur stuff.
Can I talk
about fossils?
( groans )
"Sting's son,
seven years old."
And there's a picture.
What are you reading
The Kidnapper's Guide
to Manhattan Private Schools?
No, it's New York
magazine.
It's an article about
the best schools in
the city.
So, how well do
you know Sting?
I actually haven't
even met him.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
That's too bad.
I really want to go to
his concert Friday night
but it's totally
sold out.
I know!
Why don't you
meet him...
and get tickets!
If you get two,
I'll take you.
Well, actually,
I'm picking Ben up tomorrow.
Maybe he'll be there.
There you go!
Oh, you're so lucky.
You might actually get
to meet Sting tomorrow.
That's why
you have kids.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Hi, Monica.
Hi.
Hi, boots.
See, Chandler,
I'm getting a lot of use
out of them already.
They're very practical.
See, you can wear them
with dresses
with skirts, with pants...
You can wear them with shorts
on the street corner
and earn the money
to pay for them.
Wow. They're beautiful.
They hurt so much!
What?!
The guy who made these
hates feet and wants
to see them die.
Well, give them to me.
I haven't felt my feet
in years.
I can't. I spent so
much money on them
and I told Chandler
that I wear them
all the time.
I can't just
give them away.
Well, then get your money back
and return them.
I can do that, either.
The soles are already
a little scuffed up
and the insides are filled
with my blood.
Oh.
Hi.
Hey.
Hey, I just picked up Ben
from school.
Oh.
I don't think you did
a very thorough job.
I dropped him off
at Carol's.
Anyway, it turns out
I'm not going to get
those tickets, though.
Oh, no! Why not?
Well, it turns out Ben and
Sting's son do not get along.
How come?
Apparently, Sting's son
made fun of the fact
that Ben's moms are "lesbinems."
Wait, but, Ross, if
they don't get along
then you should
smooth things over.
Make them be friends.
Phoebe, you can't force kids
to be friends.
Sure you can.
Give them some blocks.
Put them in a playpen.
Playpen?! Ben's seven.
Your kid is seven?!
He's really small.
Please, please
get the tickets.
I'm sorry, Pheebs.
I just can't do it.
Yes, you can.
Sting says so himself.
What?
( to tune of "Roxanne" ):
♪ Ross can! ♪
Look, Phe-- I'm sorry,
it's just that--
♪ Ross can! ♪
Phoebe, I...
♪ Ross can, get me
the tickets! ♪
♪ Ross can get me the tickets! ♪
Here she is--
future fashion superstar.
Oh, Joey, I'm hardly--
My little sister Deena!
Right. Hi, Deena.
Nice to meet you.
Hi.
Thanks so much
for meeting with me.
Joey's told me
so much about you.
This is so
exciting for her.
Well, I'll let you
two fash... ists
get down to business.
All right...
okay...
Okay.
All right, Deena.
Well, let's talk about
the different areas of fashion
that you could
get involved in.
Let's see, there's design--
but you may need a whole
other degree for that--
uh, there's sales,
which is great
because you get to travel...
I don't care about fashion.
I'm pregnant,
and I know you are, too
so you got to help me.
And there's marketing.
Oh, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow,
ow, ow!
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh!
Okay.
( yelping in pain )
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing, I just...
I just was yawning.
( yelping yawn )
Oh, don't forget, my office
holiday party is tonight.
Honey, we don't really have to
go to this thing tonight, do we?
Now, sweetie, I know that
you don't like my office parties
but you could wear
your new boots.
See, every cloud
has a supple leather lining.
I don't think that I want
to wear the boots tonight.
Why not?
Well, you know,
I'm just worried
that your bosses
will see them
and think they pay you
too much money.
Or your assistant will see them
and want a raise.
Do you think I work at some kind
of boot-pricing company?
Well, anyway, I've picked out
this outfit that I want to wear
and the boots don't really
go with it.
You said that you
paid all that money
because those boots
go with skirts,
dresses and pants.
Fine. And if you want me
to wear the boots
I'll wear the boots.
In fact, I'll go into
my room right now
and, you know,
try the outfit on.
Okay.
Ooh-wee!
( giggling )
Christmas party
in my boots!
( pained laughter )
I can't go in there.
I can't tell him.
Honey, it's going
to be okay.
He has been incredibly
supportive of me.
And if he gets
a little upset
that's what
the meatball sub is for.
Thank you.
Hey!
It's my fashion girls!
What's wrong?
Honey, why don't
you sit down?
Deena has something that
she wants to tell you.
Oh. What... what's going on?
Is it Mom? Is she sick?
Is it Dad's heart?
Is that a sandwich?
Joe, Mom and Dad
are fine.
Is that a sandwich?!
Joey, there's something
that you should know.
Deena?
I'm pregnant.
What?!
Now-- give him
the sandwich.
Give him the
sandwich!
Well, obviously,
this is a mistake.
You can't be pregnant
because you have to have sex
to get pregnant.
Joe, I tried to wait
until I was 25, like you did.
What?! Deena...
Oop!
Sh--
I can't believe this!
You're the good one!
You went to college!
Both years!
Who did this to you?
Bobby Corso.
But he's a
real nice guy.
I like him a lot.
He's real funny.
You got pregnant
for funny?
Deena, if he's funny,
laugh!
I'll be back in a little while.
You stay here.
Why? Where you going?
I can't look at you right now.
( heavy sigh )
Wow.
I know.
Oh, there you are, Ben.
Aunt Phoebe
what are you doing here?
Well, I heard
you're having a problem
with one of the boys
in your class
and so I thought I would just
come down here
and sit you both down,
have a little talk
and make it all okay.
Now, the boy's name
is Sting's Son.
Jack? I hate him.
He's a jerk.
Now, Ben, sometimes people may
seem like jerks on the outside
but they have famous fathers.
I have to go.
My friend Doug is
waiting for me
over there.
Him you're friends with.
Excuse me.
Can I help you
with something?
Yes. Yes, you can.
I'm looking for
Jack's parents.
Are you with one
of the students?
Uh-huh, I'm with Ben.
Are you one of Ben's mothers?
I am one of Ben's mothers.
I'm a lesbian.
It was difficult
coming out to
my parents.
Well, hi.
I'm Jenny Boone.
I'm a new teacher here.
I've only met
your partner Carol.
Ah, okay, so that would
make me Susan.
Right.
Are you looking
for Jack's parents
to discuss the problems
he's having with Ben?
Yeah, because
I really do think
the parents should
sit down together
and have a conversation.
Yeah! Let's do that!
That... that sounds good.
We should sit down
and talk.
Just me, my lover Carol
and the Stings.
Um, now, how... how will
I get in touch with them?
Oh, their number's
on the contact sheet.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Could I get
a copy of that
'cause Carol
threw it out.
She lost ours.
She's such
a scatterbrain.
But what a hot
piece of ass.
You know, that party
wasn't bad.
Yeah.
I didn't know
there'd be dancing.
That was a fun surprise.
I don't see any cabs.
Maybe we should just walk.
No, no, we can't walk.
It's, like, 15 blocks
to the subway.
Let's go.
Hey, do you think we can
get the subway right there
if we climb down through
that manhole cover?
What's going on?
I can't walk, okay?
Okay, these boots
were a huge mistake.
What?
Okay, you were right,
all right?
I never should
have bought them.
They're killing me
one toe at a time.
So I was right.
This is what it
feels like to be right.
It's oddly unsettling.
How are we going
to get home?
Maybe a piggyback ride?
Hop on.
Okay, just
give me a second.
Let me just get
my boots off first.
Oh. Oh...
Oh... oh, God.
Oh... oh... oh...
Honey, I know you're
in pain right now
but I'm a little
turned on.
Do you ever worry
that you'll be walking
and your baby will just,
like, slip out?
What college
was that, Deena?
Oh, my God.
Bobby?
Hi, Deena.
Good to see you.
Joey, what are you doing?
Just what needs to be done.
Dearly beloved, we are gathered
here to join...
Joey, this is crazy.
Don't interrupt me
when I'm talking to God.
Now, where
were we?
Oh, right, okay, do you, Deena,
take this man...
No!
Oh, you'll take him.
No, I won't.
You don't get
a say in this.
Yes, I do.
I heard "I do."
We're halfway there.
Okay, you...
All right, Joey
that is enough.
Listen, as beautiful
and moving as this
ceremony is
this is not legal, okay?
They don't have
a marriage license
they don't have
any witnesses
and the groom only
has on one shoe.
Yeah, he took
the other one off
and hit me with it.
Well, what am I
supposed to do?
You're supposed
to realize
that they are adults
and that they can make
their own decisions.
No, they can't.
They were stupid enough
to get knocked up.
Hey.
Contraceptives are not
always effective.
Right?
Yeah... we kind
of didn't use any.
Oh, come on, kids,
a little help here.
Wow. This place
is incredible.
( gasps )
Sting's pen...
that he gave to Phoebe.
( gasps )
Come on, secret passageway.
Hi.
I'm Trudy.
You must be Ben's mum.
Why else would I be here?
Do sit down.
Uh-huh.
I gather Jack and Ben
haven't been getting
along lately.
Yeah.
I'm sure there are
two sides to this story
but all I've heard is that
Ben's a bit of a poo-poo head.
Um, I'm sorry.
Won't Jack's father
be joining us?
Well, I'm sorry.
Jack's father's
not available.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Well, then could
we reschedule
for say, Friday night,
perhaps at 8:00?
Oh, no, I know
that wouldn't work.
My husband's in concert.
Concert. Yeah.
That just put us
in quite a pickle.
Because you see, I'm very busy
before and after the concert
and he's obviously busy during.
So, I guess you and I
should talk about
Jack and Ben right now.
Unless... unless, um...
okay, I would be willing
to go to the concert.
All the while, thinking about
the children, of course.
Are you here for tickets?
Thank you.
Four would be great.
Wow. I'm not giving
concert tickets
to someone who'd use
their son like this.
Oh, then you're in luck.
Ben's not my son.
Look, I've just
pressed a button
triggering
a silent alarm.
Any minute now the police
will be here.
The Police... here?
A reunion? Ooh.
Okay, ten blocks down,
five to go.
Oh, wait.
Stop, stop, stop.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Do you need a break?
My boots in tan.
Hey, can you get
a little closer
so I can see the price?
I can see it from
right here.
It'll cost you
one husband.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I think I can walk
the rest of the way now.
Just give me my boots.
I don't have
your boots.
Well, I don't
have them, either.
Where are they?
Well, why don't you
check in one of
my saddlebags
while I chew on
a bale of hay.
Okay...
We've got to go
back and get them.
Honey, are
you seriously
ever going to wear
the boots again?
I'm never going
to wear them again.
I just didn't get a chance
to say good-bye.
You know what?
You can say good-bye
to the tan ones.
Okay.
All right.
Bye, boots.
Wait!
Half off?!
Joey, just because
they're not
getting married
doesn't mean that this
is going to be a disaster.
Maybe they have
a plan.
Oh, oh, okay.
Okay, let's
hear their plan.
Now, what's the future look like
for Deena and Bobby?
Well... I really have
high hopes for my band.
You were right.
He is funny.
RACHEL:
Hey, wait a minute.
I bet when you told
people at first
that you wanted to be an actor
they laughed at you.
Come on, Bobby
why don't you tell us
a little bit about your band.
It's just me
and my pal Rooster.
The band's name
is Numb Nuts.
Really?
Deena, if you're
having a baby
you should be married.
Even if it is
to Bobby.
Dude, that's not a compliment.
You know, Joey, I knew you
wouldn't be supportive.
So, what,
what are you going to do?
You going to have
the baby
and raise it
by yourself?
Without a husband?
You can't be
a single mother alone.
You're going
to ruin your life.
Well, excuse me.
Am I ruining my life?
No, no, no,
it's different for you.
You're so strong
and together.
You're not
some dumb kid
who doesn't know
what she's doing.
Excuse me?
One pregnant woman
at a time, please.
I just want you
to be okay.
So forcing her
to marry Bobby
is going to make
that happen?
Maybe.
So, what kind
of music does
Numb Nuts...?
Aw, forget it.
I can't.
Joey...
I am scared to death about this.
But I really think
I can do it.
I'm just going
to need some help.
And Bobby's going to
be here the whole time.
You bet I am.
And to answer your
earlier question
we're straight-up
gangsta rap.
Look, Rachel's told me
how much easier
you've made all this
on her.
Why can't you do that for me?
Because... because...
because you're my baby sister.
And you're my big brother.
I mean, you're my
favorite guy
in the whole world.
I'm not even scared
to tell Mom and Dad.
I was scared of telling you.
Well, I'd be scared
of them, but all right.
Joey, I can't stand the thought
of having this baby
with you mad at me.
I want him to have his uncle.
Is my baby going to have
his Uncle Joey?
Of course he's going
to have his Uncle Joey.
We're going
to be all right.
I mean, even
if we're not married
this baby is going
to be so loved.
And not just by us.
That's right.
By his uncle, too.
And by you.
Okay, Bobby, why don't we
just come over here
and let them have
a little moment, okay?
Come here.
No, seriously,
what's wrong with you?
You're going
to love me so much.
I got Sting tickets!
Oh, my God,
I do love you!
How did you do it?
Well, let's just say...
♪ Ross can! ♪
Where are the seats?
Middle balcony.
Okay, would you say
that that's more
than 50 yards
away from Sting
his wife or a member
of his family?
Yeah.
Then that's not
breaking the law. I'm there!
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org